Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Centennial Memories Section 4, no date- (Box-folder 46-15)
- Centennial Book Cover, no date- (Box-folder 46-16)
- Wildcat Mugs and Shirt, Mideast Poster, Augmented Brochure, 1991- (Box-folder 46-17)
- Patrick-Sampler Disc 2, 1991- (Box-folder 46-18)
- Patrick-Sampler Disc 1, 1991- (Box-folder 46-19)
- Record Print, Projections Cover Page 2 Scans, no date- (Box-folder 46-20)
- Projections Cover and Page 1 Scans, no date- (Box-folder 46-21)
- Patterns Hair and Woven, no date- (Box-folder 46-22)
- Campus Map, no date- (Box-folder 46-23)
- Campus Buildings, no date- (Box-folder 46-24)
- Pat O'Hara Postcards, no date- (Box-folder 46-25)
- Maps, no date- (Box-folder 46-26)
- Campus Map Stuff, no date- (Box-folder 46-27)
- Maps and Buildings, no date- (Box-folder 46-28)
- Current Maps, no date- (Box-folder 46-29)
- Nutrition Brochure and Sampler Stuff, no date- (Box-folder 46-30)
- Reslife Scans Fall Disk 2 of 2, 1992- (Box-folder 46-31)
- Fall '91 Reslife Updated at Changes Disc 1 of 2, 1991- (Box-folder 46-32)
- Fall-Final Reslife Copy, 1991- (Box-folder 46-33)
- Miscellaneous Stuff from Fall'91 Reslife and Master Templates, 1992- (Box-folder 46-34)
- Projections Front Cover, no date- (Box-folder 46-35)
- Projections Back Up, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 46-36)
- Projections Cover Back up, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 46-37)
- Augmented Brochure, August Column, no date- (Box-folder 46-38)
- Logos Backup, no date- (Box-folder 46-39)
- Calendar Illustrations, no date- (Box-folder 46-40)
- Reslife Inside, no date- (Box-folder 46-41)
- December-January 1997 Auxiliary Productions, 1996- (Box-folder 46-42)
- April -1997 June Auxiliary Productions (Box-folder 46-43)
- ResLife, 1996- (Box-folder 46-44)
- Continuing Education, Duo Tone, 1997- (Box-folder 46-45)
- CWU Graphics, no date- (Box-folder 46-46)
- Acceptance Cover Unflat Art, no date- (Box-folder 46-47)
- CWU Graphics Productions, no date- (Box-folder 46-48)
- CWU Graphics Productions, no date- (Box-folder 46-49)
- CWU Graphics Productions, no date- (Box-folder 46-50)
- IMC 107, no date- (Box-folder 46-51)
- IMC 105, no date- (Box-folder 46-52)
- Catalog, Home Brochure, CWU IMC 11, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 46-53)
- Steve Jefferies Video Jackets, no date- (Box-folder 46-54)
- IMC 109, no date- (Box-folder 46-55)
- Printed Jobs, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 46-56)
- CWU University Book Store Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 46-57)
- Miscellaneous Back up from Quadra, no date- (Box-folder 46-58)
- Power Mac Back Up, 1997- (Box-folder 46-59)
- Media Center, Joe's Head, no date- (Box-folder 46-60)
- APS Mari Folder, 1996- (Box-folder 46-61)
- Power Mac Back Up, 1997- (Box-folder 46-62)
- Gary Vehar's Projects, no date- (Box-folder 46-63)
- CWU Graphics, no date- (Box-folder 46-64)
- CWU Media Center Production, no date- (Box-folder 46-65)
- Catalog Inside pages, no date- (Box-folder 46-66)
- Catalogue Cover, no date- (Box-folder 46-67)
- Jobs in Progress, 1997- (Box-folder 46-68)
- CWU Apartment Handout, no date- (Box-folder 46-69)
- Chimps Backed up, 1989- (Box-folder 46-70)
- ResLife Miscellaneous, 1996- (Box-folder 46-71)
- Financial Aid Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 46-72)
- Printed Jobs, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 46-73)
- Mari Aps #2, no date- (Box-folder 46-74)
- Mari Aps #1, no date- (Box-folder 46-75)
- Auxiliary Productions, 1997- (Box-folder 46-76)
- Printed Jobs, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 46-77)
- Washoe 30X40, no date- (Box-folder 46-78)
- CWU History Book RFP Chapter 2 and Sample Spread, 2007- (Box-folder 46-79)
- CTE Pieces, no date- (Box-folder 46-80)
- Theater Arts Season Brochure, Corrected, no date- (Box-folder 46-81)
- Battle in Seattle Flyer, 2004- (Box-folder 46-82)
- Summer Session Schedule Book, 2004- (Box-folder 46-83)
- CWU Center Corrected Version, no date- (Box-folder 46-84)
- Transfer Guide, no date- (Box-folder 46-85)
- Transfer Guide Updated Cover and Inside Pages, no date- (Box-folder 46-86)
- Graphics Production 6308 Season Matinee, no date- (Box-folder 46-87)
- CWU Theater Postcards and Posters, no date- (Box-folder 46-88)
- Direct Mail Letterhead and Envelop Annual Giving Pledge Card, no date- (Box-folder 46-89)
- CWU Reslife, Final Files, 2004- (Box-folder 46-90)
- Central Connections Back up Disk 1 of 2, 2005- (Box-folder 46-91)
- Central Connections Back up Disk 2 of 2, 2005- (Box-folder 46-92)
- HEP Deccio, Rubin with Students, 2003- (Box-folder 46-93)
- CWU Living Learning Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 46-94)
- Transfer Guide Images, 2003- (Box-folder 46-95)
- Running Start, Corrected Professional Certificate Program, no date- (Box-folder 46-96)
- Wildcat Habitat CWU Winter, 2004- (Box-folder 46-97)
- FBT Adult Education Guide, no date- (Box-folder 46-98)
- FBT Adult Education Guide 2nd Copy, no date- (Box-folder 46-99)
- McConnell Spotlight Large Scans, no date- (Box-folder 46-100)
- Fall-Residence Life, 2003- (Box-folder 46-101)
- Fall-Residence Life, 2003- (Box-folder 46-102)
- RH Frank, no date- (Box-folder 46-103)
- Summer Camp T-Shirt, no date- (Box-folder 46-104)
- Theater Posters and Postcards, no date- (Box-folder 46-105)
- CWU New Look PDF Files, Ads, Brochure and Inserts, Other Pieces, no date- (Box-folder 46-106)
- Heather Bries, Migori; Kenya, Mfangango, Kenya; Kisii, Tanzania, 2004- (Box-folder 46-107)
- For a Better Tomorrow, Adult Education Guide, no date- (Box-folder 46-108)
- CWU AFROTC Brochure, 2003- (Box-folder 46-109)
- Kamola Reopening Program, 2003- (Box-folder 46-110)
- HEP Brochures, no date- (Box-folder 46-111)
- Kamola Alumni Scrapbook Scans 2, 2003- (Box-folder 46-112)
- Bird Woman Postcard, HEP English, no date- (Box-folder 46-113)
- West Side Poster and Postcard, no date- (Box-folder 46-114)
- CWU Acceptance Book #1, no date- (Box-folder 46-115)
- Men's, Women's Basketball, 2006- (Box-folder 46-116)
- Bret's CD-President's Speaker, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 46-117)
- Battle in Seattle 18X24 Poster, no date- (Box-folder 46-118)
- Acceptance Book #1, 2003- (Box-folder 46-119)
- CWU Variety, President's PowerPoint Presentation, 2004- (Box-folder 46-120)
- CWU International Newsletter, no date- (Box-folder 46-121)
- CWU Financial Aid Handbook, no date- (Box-folder 46-122)
- Fall-CWU Residence Life, no date- (Box-folder 46-123)
- Battle in Seattle, Postcard and Poster, 2004- (Box-folder 46-124)
- CHCI Postcard, no date- (Box-folder 46-125)
- CWU University Store Coupon Updates, no date- (Box-folder 46-126)
- Graphic Productions- 1995-1997 Deep Sea Daze, 1996 Miscellaneous Mari SyQuest, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 46-127)
- Bret's Desktop Stuff, Back up, 2005- (Box-folder 46-128)
- Variety, 2002- (Box-folder 46-129)
- "2004" Acceptance Book #2, 2003- (Box-folder 46-130)
- CWU Housing Jobs: Wildcat Connections, Welcome Poster, no date- (Box-folder 46-131)
- Completed Jobs, Greatest Hits 2 of 2, 1999- (Box-folder 46-132)
- Back up of Miscellaneous Jobs in Progress, no date- (Box-folder 46-133)
- Miscellaneous Job Pieces 2 From Bret's Mac, 2007- (Box-folder 46-134)
- Library Sample Photos, no date- (Box-folder 46-135)
- Back up, Residence Housing, 2007- (Box-folder 46-136)
- Back up, Residence Housing, 2007- (Box-folder 46-137)
- Back up, Residence Housing, 2007- (Box-folder 46-138)
- Back up, Residence Housing, 2007- (Box-folder 46-139)
- Papss Program 1st Run, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 46-140)
- Papss Program 1st Run, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 46-141)
- Fraser and Haas, no date- (Box-folder 46-142)
- Joe Esherick, no date- (Box-folder 46-143)
- Nance's Old Jobs 3, no date- (Box-folder 46-144)
- Nance's Old Jobs 3, no date- (Box-folder 46-145)
- Orchestra Posters, no date- (Box-folder 46-146)
- Nance's Old Jobs 2, Fonts off Her Old Mac, no date- (Box-folder 46-147)
- Nance's Old Jobs 1, no date- (Box-folder 46-148)
- Nance's Old Jobs 1, no date- (Box-folder 46-149)
- Nance's Old Jobs 2, Fonts off Her Old Mac, no date- (Box-folder 46-150)
- Miscellaneous Job Pieces 1 From Bret's Mac, 2007- (Box-folder 46-151)
- Bret Miscellaneous Old Stuff, no date- (Box-folder 46-152)
- CWU Showdown Ads, Large Color, Large Black and White, Quarter Black and White, 2005- (Box-folder 46-153)
- Darwin Davis "With Whim and a Wham" 1960s-2005, 2006- (Box-folder 46-154)
- Reslife Fall 04 Corrected, 2004- (Box-folder 46-155)
- Central Connections on Air, no date- (Box-folder 46-156)
- Final President's Report Collected, no date- (Box-folder 46-157)
- CWU Teaching at a Distance, no date- (Box-folder 46-158)
- Dr. Wendy Bohrson Hawaii 2010 Field Research, Raw Footage, no date- (Box-folder 46-159)
- Mammoth Proportional, no date- (Box-folder 46-160)
- CWU Acceptance Book 1, no date- (Box-folder 46-161)
- CWU Acceptance Book Images 2, no date- (Box-folder 46-162)
- President's Report Back up, 2005- (Box-folder 46-163)
- President's Report, 2005- (Box-folder 46-164)
- President's Report Collected, 2005- (Box-folder 46-165)
- Beacon, no date- (Box-folder 46-166)
- Field Trip Dan Beck, 2003- (Box-folder 46-167)
- Acceptance Book #2, 2003- (Box-folder 46-168)
- Theater Back up, 2005- (Box-folder 46-169)
- Miscellaneous Stuff, 2004- (Box-folder 46-170)
- Advising Handbook Images, no date- (Box-folder 46-171)
- Graduate Studies and Research Brochure, 2003- (Box-folder 46-172)
- Completed Jobs, 4641 International Advertisement, 4911 Theatre/Kamola Flyer, 4913 Admissions Table Drape, 4915 Reach PowerPoint, Miscellaneous Images, Miscellaneous Zips, 2003- (Box-folder 46-173)
- KC in the Kitchen, 2007- (Box-folder 46-174)
- KC in the Kitchen, 2007- (Box-folder 46-175)
- Collected International Brochure, 2004- (Box-folder 46-176)
- Student Outreach Article, Student Outreach Photos, 2006- (Box-folder 46-177)
- President's Report, Images, 2004- (Box-folder 46-178)
- CWU Centers Brochure, 2005- (Box-folder 46-179)
- #51-#108 (Box-folder 47-1)
- #110 (Box-folder 47-2)
- #112-#318 (Box-folder 47-3)
- #319-#320 (Box-folder 48-1)
- #322-#325 (Box-folder 48-2)
- #329-#455 (Box-folder 48-3)
- #457-#459 (Box-folder 48-4)
- #462-#464 (Box-folder 48-5)
- #466 (Box-folder 48-6)
- #469-#476 (Box-folder 48-7)
- #478 (Box-folder 48-8)
- #480-#549 (Box-folder 48-9)
- #551-#610 (Box-folder 48-10)
- #611-#615 (Box-folder 49-1)
- #616-#713 (Box-folder 49-2)
- #716-#765 (Box-folder 49-3)
- #775 (Box-folder 49-4)
- #777 (Box-folder 49-5)
- #780 (Box-folder 49-6)
- #782-#804 (Box-folder 49-7)
- #326 (Box-folder 50-1)
- #327 (Box-folder 50-2)
- #328 (Box-folder 50-3)
- #467 (Box-folder 50-4)
- #468 (Box-folder 50-5)
- #477 (Box-folder 50-6)
- #479 (Box-folder 50-7)
- #507 (Box-folder 50-8)
- #522 (Box-folder 50-9)
- #529 (Box-folder 50-10)
- #547-#580 (Box-folder 50-11)
- #582-#584 (Box-folder 50-12)
- #615-#624 (Box-folder 50-13)
- #636-#719 (Box-folder 50-14)
- #732-#805 (Box-folder 50-15)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 1 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-16)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 2 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-17)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 3 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-18)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 4 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-19)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 5 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-20)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 6 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-21)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 7 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-22)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 8 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-23)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 9 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-24)
- Extra copy of Old Job Pieces Bret disc 10 of 10, 2008- (Box-folder 50-25)
- Admissions Search Piece, 2009- (Box-folder 50-26)
- Admissions Completed Jobs, 2009- (Box-folder 50-27)
- Completed Jobs Disk 1 Housing, 2009- (Box-folder 50-28)
- Completed Jobs Disk 2 Housing, 2009- (Box-folder 50-29)
- Completed Jobs Disk 3 Housing, 2009- (Box-folder 50-30)
- Completed Jobs Disk 4 Housing, 2009- (Box-folder 50-31)
- Completed Jobs Disk 5 Housing, 2009- (Box-folder 50-32)
- Completed Jobs Disk 6 Housing Handbooks, 2009- (Box-folder 50-33)
- Completed Jobs Disk 7 Housing Signup Materials, 2009- (Box-folder 50-34)
- Completed Jobs /Discover, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 50-35)
- Completed Jobs Reslife Spring, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 50-36)
- Completed jobs Discover Orientation Handbook 08, 2009- (Box-folder 50-37)
- Completed Jobs Discover Handbook 09, 2009- (Box-folder 50-38)
- Miscellaneous Completed Jobs Disk 3, 2009- (Box-folder 50-39)
- Miscellaneous Completed Jobs Disk 4, 2009- (Box-folder 50-40)
- Miscellaneous Completed Jobs Disk 5, 2009- (Box-folder 50-41)
- Miscellaneous Completed Jobs Disk 6, 2009- (Box-folder 50-42)
- Miscellaneous Completed Jobs Living History Brochure Disk 7, 2009- (Box-folder 50-43)
- Miscellaneous Completed Jobs Miscellaneous Disk 9, 2009- (Box-folder 50-44)
- Completed Jobs Music at Benaroya Disk 1, 2009- (Box-folder 50-45)
- Completed Jobs Music at Benaroya Disk 2, 2009- (Box-folder 50-46)
- Completed Jobs 35th Anniversary Beacon 1, 2009- (Box-folder 50-47)
- Completed Jobs 35th Anniversary Beacon 2, 2009- (Box-folder 50-48)
- Completed Jobs 35th Anniversary Beacon 3, 2009- (Box-folder 50-49)
- Admissions Search Piele, 2009- (Box-folder 50-50)
- Completed Jobs Transfer 10 Master Pages, 2009- (Box-folder 50-51)
- Completed Jobs Alumni Newsletters Spring 2009, Winter 2010, Spring 2010, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 50-52)
- Completed Jobs Admissions Viewbook 2009 (Box-folder 50-53)
- Completed Jobs Admissions Viewbook 2009 (Box-folder 50-54)
- Completed Jobs Transfer Search 10, 2009- (Box-folder 50-55)
- Completed Jobs Beacon Winter, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 50-56)
- Olga Web Job Files, 2010- (Box-folder 50-57)
- Completed Jobs Disk1: Development, Alumni, Theater, 2010- (Box-folder 50-58)
- Completed Jobs Disk 2 Various Jobs, 2010- (Box-folder 50-59)
- Completed Jobs Development Color Tests, 2010- (Box-folder 50-60)
- Completed Jobs College of Business, 2010- (Box-folder 50-61)
- Completed Jobs PESPH 1, 2010- (Box-folder 50-62)
- Completed Jobs PESPH 2, 2010- (Box-folder 50-63)
- Completed Jobs PESPH 3, 2010- (Box-folder 50-64)
- Hats Off Photos Disk 1 Only Copy, no date- (Box-folder 50-65)
- Hats Off Photos Disk 2 Only Copy, no date- (Box-folder 50-66)
- Portraits Spring/ Summer, 2011- (Box-folder 50-67)
- CWAS Goldendale Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 50-68)
- CWAS Goldendale Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 50-69)
- CWAS Goldendale Disc 3, 2011- (Box-folder 50-70)
- Discover Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 50-71)
- Discover Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 50-72)
- Kamola Hall Centennial Logo, no date- (Box-folder 50-73)
- Smith Lashier Cello, 2011- (Box-folder 50-74)
- Ichm Wadesz Photoshop Channels book, no date- (Box-folder 50-75)
- Movers and Shakers, 2011- (Box-folder 50-76)
- BU, 2004- (Box-folder 50-77)
- Miscellaneous CT 2 of 3 3139 Commencement 2, no date- (Box-folder 50-78)
- 3 of 3 6139 Commencement 3, no date- (Box-folder 50-79)
- Completed Jobs No Number March, 2012- (Box-folder 50-80)
- CWU Central Today, 1993- (Box-folder 50-81)
- Springtime JAZ 2GB, no date- (Box-folder 50-82)
- FOW Brochure Uprint with Artwork, no date- (Box-folder 51-1)
- Transfer Acceptance, 2002- (Box-folder 51-2)
- Reslife Fall 02 #2, 2002- (Box-folder 51-3)
- Pride has a Place #1, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 51-4)
- Departmental Bros, Basketball Press book, Institute for Science and Technology, Kelton Knight, Paragon Video Box Template, Provost, Rodeo Ad, Douglas Honors, Jennifer's files, Lacre Programs, 1996- (Box-folder 51-5)
- Champ Final Images, CT Images, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 51-6)
- Discover Peechee, Centers Pee Chee, COB Ad for WA CEO Magazine, 2004 Economic Outlook, Tuition Waiver Brief (Box-folder 51-7)
- Beacon, Beacon, 2004- (Box-folder 51-8)
- Theater, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 51-9)
- Back Up: Files from Old Macs (Only Copy Back up From Jaz Disk), no date- (Box-folder 51-10)
- Miscellaneous Stuff From Jaz (Bret) (Only Copy-From Jaz Disk), no date- (Box-folder 51-11)
- Miscellaneous Apps from Jaz (Bret) (Only Copy-From Jaz Disk), no date- (Box-folder 51-12)
- Miscellaneous Back up of: Bret's Apps from Old CPU 2 of 2 Only Copy-From Jaz Disk, no date- (Box-folder 51-13)
- Miscellaneous Back up of: Bret's Apps from Old CPU 1 of 2 Only Copy-From Jaz Disk, no date- (Box-folder 51-14)
- Miscellaneous Back up of: Miscellaneous Old Apps and System Bret Only Copy-From Jaz Disk, no date- (Box-folder 51-15)
- CWU Library Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-16)
- CWU Transfer Accept 2, no date- (Box-folder 51-17)
- Transfer Student Newsletter, 2002- (Box-folder 51-18)
- From Printer Zips and Miscellaneous, Only Copy, 2001- (Box-folder 51-19)
- From Printer Zips and Miscellaneous, Only Copy, 2001- (Box-folder 51-20)
- Camp Project Old Files, no date- (Box-folder 51-21)
- Transfer Acceptance CWU 1, no date- (Box-folder 51-22)
- Revised Parent Guide, National Guard Brochure/Flyer, no date- (Box-folder 51-23)
- CWU Ad for Mariner Yearbook, no date- (Box-folder 51-24)
- CWU Theater, 2003- (Box-folder 51-25)
- Competency Block, Miscellaneous Files, 2009- (Box-folder 51-26)
- CWU Competency Block Brochure, 2003- (Box-folder 51-27)
- Updated Camp Brochures and Flyers, 2003- (Box-folder 51-28)
- Spring Reslife Out, 2003- (Box-folder 51-29)
- History Brochure Images, no date- (Box-folder 51-30)
- From Printer Zips, 2003- (Box-folder 51-31)
- Printer Zips, 2003- (Box-folder 51-32)
- CWU Billboards 1, no date- (Box-folder 51-33)
- CWU Transfer Acceptance #1, 2004- (Box-folder 51-34)
- CWU Transfer Acceptance #2, 2004- (Box-folder 51-35)
- CWU Transfer Acceptance #3, 2004- (Box-folder 51-36)
- CWU Apartment Brochure, 2004- (Box-folder 51-37)
- CWU Housing Re-App "Here's the Dirt", 2004- (Box-folder 51-38)
- Summer Teaser, 2005- (Box-folder 51-39)
- Basketball Cards, no date- (Box-folder 51-40)
- Summer Session Teaser Corrected File, no date- (Box-folder 51-41)
- CWU Summer Handbook, no date- (Box-folder 51-42)
- Computer Science Corrections, no date- (Box-folder 51-43)
- CWU Billboards 2, 2005- (Box-folder 51-44)
- CWU Summer Session Poster, no date- (Box-folder 51-45)
- New Look Final, 2003- (Box-folder 51-46)
- Miscellaneous Backups, Accept Book Images 2, CWU Parent Guide, Old Business Greeting, Old Theatre Program Ads, no date- (Box-folder 51-47)
- CWU Accept Book Disk 1, Copy of Was Sent to Printer, no date- (Box-folder 51-48)
- Old File President Report, 1998- (Box-folder 51-49)
- Revised Residence Life, 2005- (Box-folder 51-50)
- Central Scores! CWU Department of Music, 2003- (Box-folder 51-51)
- Jobs for Abbotts, CWU Residence Hall Brochure, CWU Apartment Brochure, MET Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-52)
- CWU Transfer Guide, no date- (Box-folder 51-53)
- Camp, no date- (Box-folder 51-54)
- Transfer Guide, Application and Envelope, no date- (Box-folder 51-55)
- New Scans for Rosario/Adrian Poster, 2002- (Box-folder 51-56)
- Rich's Mammoth Picks, no date- (Box-folder 51-57)
- Miscellaneous Zip Backup, Summer Session, WLA Reg. Booklet Bret, Contract Negs, Legislative Brief Re-Do's, Letterhead Negs, Library Conference Brochure, 2003- (Box-folder 51-58)
- CWU Commencement, 2003- (Box-folder 51-59)
- Posada Postcard, no date- (Box-folder 51-60)
- Disk #24 Dining: Housing Coupons 42830212, Easter Desserts 2012, Parent Weekend Brunch, Blast from the Past 2012, Website Logos: Apple, CWU new PDF, Ellensburg Downtown, Jostens, NACUFS, Wildcat Shop (Box-folder 51-61)
- Wildcat Shop: Sales, Yard Sale 2007-2008, 2007 Turkey Sale, 2007 Holiday Sale, 2009 Spring Sale, 2010 Fire Sale, 2010 Black Friday Sale, Sports Displays/Promos, Mariner Giveaway, 2010 Battle in Seattle, 2008 Crimson and Black T Shirt, Volleyball Tournament, Football Playoffs, 2007 Basketball Tournament, 2010 Welcome Center Fall, 2010 Basketball Display (Box-folder 51-62)
- Stock Photos, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 51-63)
- Stock Photos, 2010- (Box-folder 51-64)
- Disc 4 Wildcat Shop: General Merchandise, Apple Product Flyers, Product Folder Complete, Ads Only, Christian Lander, Earth Day 2007, Magnet Ad 2010, Old News Ads 2006, Sports Calendar Ad 2010, Annual Events, Holiday Closures 1/2007-2/2001, Graduation 2007, Discover 2007 (Box-folder 51-65)
- News Ads 2006, Sports Calendar Ad 2010, Annual Events, Holiday Closures 1/2007-2/2001, Graduation 2007, Discover 2007, 2001-2010 (Box-folder 51-66)
- Disc 9 Wildcat Shop: 2010 Basketball Window, 2011 Cold Weather Zone, 2008 Halloween, 2009 Save the Bags, 2010 Wellington's Best Buy, 2009 Wildcat Pride Display (Box-folder 51-67)
- Disc 8 Wildcat Shop: 2010 Wine Event, 2011 Buyback Winter, Unused: Online Order Thank You, Redesign Samples, Welcome to CWU; Displays: 2008-2009 Valentines, 2008 Musical Crimson and Black, 2008 No Water Bottles, 2009 Welcome Banners, 2009 Friday Frenzy, 2009-2010 Mother's Day, I Bleed Crimson (Box-folder 51-68)
- Disc 7 Wildcat Shop: Annual Events: 2010 Grad Finale, 2008 Wine Event, 2009 Spring Event, 2009 Wine Event, 2010 Spring Event; Displays: 2007 Cat and Dog, 2008 Psycho Disclaimer, 2010 Used Books, 2009 Welcome Pennants; Buyback: 2007 Series, 2009 June Series; Milk It from Vendor: 2010 Milk It November, 2010 Poster December (Box-folder 51-69)
- Disc 6 Wildcat Shop: Annual Events, 2009 Discover, 2009 Grad Finale, 2010 Discover (Box-folder 51-70)
- Disc 5 Wildcat Shop: Annual Events,2008 Graduation,2008 Grad Finale; Coupons: Free T Online, 2010 General 25% Off, 2010 Halloween, 2011 Horizons, 2011 Basketball Showdown, 2009-2010; Welcome Center: 2007 Westside, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 51-71)
- Disc 10 Wildcat Shop: CWU and Community, Chimposium Gift Shop,2010 August Community Event; CWU Advising Banner: 2008-2009 Employee M/Y Display, 2010 Football Roundup, 2008 Homecoming Towel Banner, 2011 Flip Flop Art; Other Staff Work:2006 Battle in Seattle, Buyback Hours, Kamola and Sue Lombard Art, Name Tags, 2006 Flyers and prior,2010 Valentine, Cap and Gown, Store History, 2010 Discovery, Employee of the Month, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 51-72)
- Disc 3 Wildcat Shop: General Books, Breast Cancer Awareness, Cat in the Hat, Chimp Totes, College Store Magazine, 2009-2011 CWU 2-Year Calendar, Entertaining, First Amendment, First Nation Month,2007 Grad, 2007 Harry Potter,2007 Hispanic Heritage, Hot and Cold: Images,2007 Clearance, 2007-2008 Women's History, Poetry Month, CWU Planner images, 2007 Spring Cleaning, General Merchandise, Apple Contract, Computer Accessories, CWU Notepaper, Microsoft License Agree, Rock the Campus, Sale Signs, Apple News Ad, Free Hewitt Packard Card, Hewitt Packard Mini Ad, Nike Plus, Pen Display, Recycle Area, Tune Your Run, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 51-73)
- Mari Back Up, 1999- (Box-folder 51-74)
- Mari Back Up, 1999- (Box-folder 51-75)
- Mari Back Up, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 51-76)
- Mari Back Up, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 51-77)
- Disc 1 OT Other: Financial Aid Postcard, Career Services Brochure, Ellenburg Downtown, EDA Logo, Observer Media Kit draft Comm, Logos complete; Catering: Wellington's Sign, Wedding Catering Brochure; Dining: Usable Photos, 2011 Deep Sea Daze, Credit Cards sign, Duty Checklists, 2011 Grad Dinner Invite,2011 Mardi Gras, Meal Plan Table Topper, Season Favorites Table Topper, 2010- (Box-folder 51-78)
- Disc 1 D Dining: Backstage Coffeehouse Design, Backstage Ad Series, Backstage Sandwich Boards, Beans for Deans 2010, Holiday Dinner 2010, Oktoberfest 2010, Open Forum Poster (Box-folder 51-79)
- Logos, Stock Phone List, New Faculty Meeting, Gift Box Stamp, Roslyn Card, no date- (Box-folder 51-80)
- Disc 13 Wildcat Shop: Welcome Center Winter 2011 Artwork for Personnel, General Sale signs; Unused: Backpack Banner Background Art, Jewelry Tags, Cancer Ribbon, Window Display, Winter Sale, Kamola Birthday Contest Ad, 2010- (Box-folder 51-81)